- What are you gonna cook?
- Your favourite.
What, again?
- Well, this is the last one.
- What, you mean no more tomatoes?
You can never have
enough tins of tomatoes, eh?
Instead...
we've got five tins of chickpeas.
That should last at least five year, eh?
- Fancy a glass of wine?
- Yeah, that'd be great.
We're in luck.
Drinkable.
- You all right, sweetheart?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Well, I'm not fine, it's all fucked, but...
- Our children are safe, aren't they?
- Totally. Yeah.
Thank God we paid for that school trip.
Imagine if we hadn't!
I can't. I can't imagine. I can't imagine.
And I don't want to imagine. I don't...
Listen, they're far, far away.
And they're safe and sound.
OK?
- Yeah.
OK.
Don't worry...
gorgeous.
Not interrupting, am I?
No.
I found this in the cellar.
I'd forgotten all about it.
I thought we could have them after dinner.
Yeah.
- It smells wonderful.
- And is that a bottle of wine, Don?
- It is indeed, Geoff.
- Thank you.
There's chocolate for after,
courtesy of your good wife.
What have we here? I get blackberries.
Vanilla. Notes of autumn.
Karen?
He'll be hungry.
When he gets back
he'll want something to eat.
- Here we go again.
- Jacob, no.
Let me tell you something. It's five days
since your boyfriend ran out on us.
If he's still breathing,
he won't be interested in pasta.
Jacob!
- It'll be your fucking neck!
- Don't say that!
- Out of order, Jacob.
- Why?
We all know it's true.
The sooner she faces it, the better.
There are no survivors.
It's just us in here and them out there.
- Sam?
- Quiet!
- God, it's a boy.
- Wait, wait. You don't know who's out there.
- Please, let me in!
- Don, it's a kid!
Help! Let me in!
Bloody hell.
- Please! Please, let me in!
- We're coming.
Let me in!
Please! Help! Let me in!
Please!
Get in. Come on, get in. Come here.
- Are you all right? Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Where have you come from?
- Sandford.
Sandford's upriver a few miles.
- How did you get here?
- They were chasing me. Screaming.
I was scared. I ran.
I tried other houses.
They were empty.
I came through the woods
and I followed the river until I got here.
- Who were chasing you?
- My mum.
My dad.
They're trying to kill me.
- There's others, too.
- How many?
- Loads.
- Sam?
- It's got me! It's got my arm!
- Karen, no!
Help me!
Alice! Get outta here!
Get down the escape hatch, go! Go!
- Geoff, I can't see. I can't see!
- Hold onto my hand!
Die, you fucker! Die!
Come back!
Oh, God!
Keep going. Follow Jacob.
Keep going. Sally, there's no time.
- We can't leave them!
- Sally, come on!
Go!
Oh, no! Shit! Fuck!
Where are you?
- Where are you?
- Alice! Alice, no! Alice!
Geoff, come on!
Come on!
Geoff!
Sally, give me your hand.
Give me your hand, Sally!
No! Jacob! Help me!
Alice! Alice!
- Where are you?
- Come on! Leave him!
- I see him there!
- Leave him!
Let go! Quick!
Don! Help us!
Don!
Get in there!
Jacob!
Come on!
Dear God!
Jacob!
Oh, fuck. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Welcome to London.
Hey, Doyle, you having fun down there?
You can kiss my ass.
This is the worst combat I ever saw.
Where's the combat?
I hear you.
- Give me something to shoot.
- Too easy.
North-east of med centre,
20th floor, three windows in.
- Fat guy jerking off in the toilet.
- Oh, bug-nuts. Him again.
I don't see him.
Where is Fester Fucknut?
His dick in his hand on the 20th floor.
Next to the fire exit.
I think he needs a jerk-off extender.
Doyle, you're the expert
in hand-to-hand combat.
- Man-to-man combat.
- Shut up.
- Think it might be your dad, Doyle.
- You got me.
Shit.
- Colonel Phillips here. What is your status?
- Good morning, Colonel.
- Morning.
- I'm watching the new arrivals disembark.
Yes, Major?
- It'll take all morning to process them.
- Copy.
No one told me that
we're now admitting children.
Just follow around to your right.
Green and brown. Interesting iris variation.
It's usually hereditary.
Do one of your parents have the same?
My mother. She did.
- How old are you, Andy?
- 12.
I think that makes you
the youngest person in the country.
Well, your blood pressure is A-OK
and you're negative
on any serious diseases or afflictions.
I think you're OK to come in.
Welcome back to Britain.
We are headed for our area
of security and reconstruction
designated as District One.
District One is located on the Isle of Dogs.
Although the Isle of Dogs is completely safe,
the surrounding area of London is not.
Large numbers of bodies are still not cleared
from the original outbreak of infection.
Rats and wild dogs are prevalent,
as is disease.
New arrivals are reminded
for their own safety
it is absolutely forbidden to cross the river
and leave the security zone.
You will be joining 15,000 civilians
who are already resident in District One.
As we approach your new home, you'll notice
a dramatically increased military presence.
The US Army is responsible for your safety.
We will do everything we can do
to make your repatriation as easy as possible.
Inside District One, however,
we believe you'll be pleasantly surprised.
We have hot and cold running water,
24-hour electricity,
a medical centre,
a supermarket and even a pub.
We're nearly home.
- Dad! Dad!
- It's Dad! Come on.
- Are you excited?
- Yeah.
I missed you so much.
Are you all right? Are you all right?
Guys. I never thought
I'd see you again, you know that?
Let's get something to eat.
I should have been notified
before children were brought in.
We've not established
the protocol for minors.
We have issues of disease and sanitation.
We don't fully understand the virus yet.
We understand that it did not manage
to go cross-species,
that it did not manage to go airborne and that
the last infected human died six months ago.
- We weren't here six months ago.
- Major.
- What are you afraid of?
- What if it comes back?
- It won't come back.
- What if it does?
If it comes back, we kill it.
Code Red.
Come on, guys.
What about this place, then, Andy?
Yeah, it's pretty good, Dad.
Look at the camera.
This way. Come through.
It's 25 floors. We've got the penthouse
up there. Believe me.
ID, sir. Thank you.
- So, what do you do here, Dad?
- What do I do? I'm a section officer.
I keep the lights on, the water running,
the heat running. See this? Look.
That says triple A - "access all areas''.
That's me. I basically run the place, you know.
No. You're the caretaker really, aren't you?
No, I run the place.
Like it?
- It's amazing!
- Even better than sunny Spain?
You ought to have seen the camps. There
were 20 in each tent and chemical toilets.
- Everything smelled of piss.
- Nice.
We'll be moving to a new house soon.
A couple of months, in fact.
A new house?
Yeah.
Listen, I hope you guys understand.
We're not gonna be able
to go back to our old house.
It's outside the security zone and I don't think
I'd want to go back there, even if I could.
What happened, Dad? To Mum?
Yeah.
Do you wanna sit down
and I'll tell you all about it?
Your mum and I were hiding in a house.
A wee cottage.
It was an old couple that owned it
and they were there, too.
Three other people.
And we were...
just trying to stay alive, I suppose.
We were doing OK for a while.
And then we were attacked.
They came in through the kitchen window.
They were really fast, you know.
Chased us.
Chased your mum.
And we were trapped.
Trapped in the bedroom.
Don!
And I see...
I see them...
biting her.
I couldn't do anything.
I tried to go back.
She was already gone.
Was there nothing you could do?
No, there was nothing I could do.
I managed to get away.
Just running, running, running...
I got to this military camp.
And you know the rest. You know I've been
in quarantine waiting for you to come back.
We're just happy you're still alive.
I'm sorry.
Doyle...
- Doyle, you bastard.
- Boy, I've never seen you get so white.
- Fuck you.
- Good morning.
Yeah, fuck outta here, man.
I'm having all good dreams.
Sunday afternoon, clear blue skies,
I'm laying in bed with my wife...
And now I'm back in this shithole.
- I know.
- Yeah?
I had that same dream about your wife.
- Quit fucking with me.
- Get outta here.
- All right. Next time I'm gonna shoot you.
- All right. See you later, family man.
I told you, I'm gonna shoot you.
What's on the TV tonight?
Are you OK? Bad dream?
I get worried I'm gonna forget
what she looks like.
You won't forget.
I don't even have a picture of her.
Promise?
Yeah.
Andy, we agreed.
You heard what they said.
It's only dogs and rats out there.
We'll get what we want and come back again.
- We should've told Dad.
- It's fine. Trust me.
They won't even know we're gone.
Where are you going?
Base, come in. We have two strays
who slipped out the north gate.
- Stray dogs?
- No, puppies.
- Yeah!
Yes! Yeah!
London's mine!
That's what we need.
Yeah, if it had keys.
Wait here.
Let's go.
There you go.
Tam!
Tam?
Tammy, are you there?
Tammy!
Tammy, this is stupid.
You're not being funny.
I knew it.
You're hurting me!
No! No! No! No!
No, don't go! No!
No!
Doyle.
I got your puppies.
No!
Get off me! Get off me!
I apologise for these precautions.
It's standard protocol with any survivors,
though we haven't had to do it for a while.
The last survivor we came across
was over two months ago.
Can you tell me anything
about how you managed to keep alive
while you were gone so long?
Do you know of any other survivors?
OK.
I'm just going to take a blood sample.
It won't hurt.
Have you come into direct contact
with the infected?
OK.
I want to see my children.
Of course. Of course.
- Mr Harris.
- Yeah.
- We've found your kids.
- Oh, thank God. Thank you so much.
We found your wife, too.
Can they hear me?
- So, what do you two think you're playing at?
- You said you saw her die.
- What?
- You said you saw her die!
- I didn't say that.
- You did. You did.
Baby, I didn't use those words.
This is... I don't know.
I mean, it's confusing, you know.
It's... it's very hard
for you to imagine, you know?
- I... It's too hard to explain.
- Well, try to explain it, Dad! Try!
Try? What do you want me to say?
I thought I saw Mum... die.
Or I wouldn't have told you that.
I was sure.
Look, guys, I'm not sure
what's happening here...
but it's good. OK?
That's the point. Mum's alive.
I want to see her!
There's no question, sir.
She has the virus. She's infected.
Why isn't she showing any symptoms?
- I don't know.
- Speculate.
A genetic abnormality which acts
as some sort of natural immunity?
But the virus is still in her blood and saliva,
so technically she's not immune.
She's a carrier.
She has the ability to infect others?
Yes, sir. Absolutely.
If this woman has natural immunity
she is incredibly valuable.
Her blood could contain
the key to a vaccine, even a cure.
Alice.
Hey, baby.
Oh, I'm so sorry. I was scared.
I shouldn't have run away.
I was scared.
Please forgive me.
Please, sir. We need time to study her.
We need to run some tests.
You can run tests on her corpse, Major.
I love you, Don.
Yeah.
Oh, God, I love you, too.
Don!
Clear channels to control room.
Control room, this is General Stone.
All forces under my control, prepare
to execute Code Red on my command.
- Affirmative.
Break, break, break, all stations.
Sunray in 30 seconds.
We have an outbreak in the med centre.
All units, safeties off.
- Affirmative.
- Open air cav transmission.
- Prepare containment areas.
- Move civilians to containment areas.
Command personnel secure in bunker.
Confirm order to lock down.
Lockdown confirmed.
Execute Code Red.
Flynn, come in. Flynn, do you hear
that Code Red or am I losing my shit?
I was about to ask the same thing.
Ten-hut!
Everything's fine. Don't worry.
I'll be back in a moment.
- It's probably nothing.
- Tam, it didn't sound like nothing.
He said he'd be back in a moment.
Are you OK? Let's go.
Come on.
- Move, move, move! Let's go!
- Andy, keep hold of my hand.
OK, come on. Keep it moving.
Come on, people. Come on.
- Don't push.
- Sir, all civilians into the containment area.
These kids are with me. It's important they are
kept protected. I need to get them out of here.
- Sir, no exceptions. It's a Code Red.
- I know what it is. My name is...
- Andy!
- Scarlet!
Andy!
- Tammy!
- Andy!
- Andy, wait!
- Scarlet!
- Just wait, Andy! We're coming!
- Calm down.
Move down. Move down the room.
Keep moving. Go, go, go. Come on.
- You think it's a drill?
- Of course not. Someone saw an infected.
Keep moving. That's it.
Good, good. Let's go.
- Why are you sealing us inside?
- For your protection.
- Just guard the door. Don't lock it.
- It's for your own protection.
- We've got to find Andy.
- We'll find him.
- Shut down civilian areas.
- Sector one, lockdown.
- Sector eight, lockdown.
- Sector three, lockdown.
Switch to emergency lighting.
Use of non-lethal force authorised.
All snipers in position.
- Ground forces to med centre.
- Ground force to med centre.
Sector one covered.
Everyone, stay calm.
Dad.
No! My dad... my dad!
He's in here!
No!
Containment area, containment area,
move into position.
No!
I confirm, only target infected.
Roger that. Only target infected.
Targeting right. I've had two down.
Watch out for the friendlies.
I can't get a shot.
Oh, man, this is FUBAR.
We got a group there at 12 o'clock.
- We've got one at three o'clock.
- On the ground, got four.
16 down.
I got two by the Jeep.
- Jesus.
- I don't see who's a target.
On the move! On the move!
Moving right! Moving right!
I can't find
the designated target here.
I cannot be target-specific.
Whisky Three, why have you stopped firing?
Come in.
Abandon selective targeting.
Shoot everything. Targets are now free.
We've lost control.
All units, all units, this is Medical
Commanding Officer Sierra Lima.
Please be on the lookout for a young boy,
age 12, name, Andy.
If he is located he must be immediately
evacuated from the containment zone.
We have to find Andy.
- We have to find him!
- It's OK. It's OK.
We're gonna find him, OK?
We're gonna find him, I promise.
I'm gonna get him out of here.
I'm gonna get you both out of here. Trust me.
- New shot.
- Abandon selective targeting.
- Confirm order?
- Target everyone at ground level.
No exceptions. Repeat, no exceptions.
Come on!
Three down.
One of ours down there. Three o'clock.
- Taking them down.
- Left sector, three o'clock.
Kid! Over here!
- I got him.
- Well, take him out. Take him out.
Doyle, I got two fuckers on me!
Fuck.
Fuck!
Tam?
This is madness.
- What's happening?
- They're shooting everybody.
- Why? It makes no sense.
- It makes perfect sense.
It's Code Red.
I saw Dad.
Where?
He's one of them.
Step one, kill the infected.
Step two, containment.
If containment fails...
step three, extermination.
Now they won't stop until everyone is dead.
So what do we do?
I mean, I'm not sitting around here
to get exterminated.
We've gotta get outta here.
If we take one step out of that door,
if the infected don't get us, the snipers will.
Well, you don't have a choice, my friend.
Right now it's dark out there. The snipers
can see you through their night scopes,
but at least you have
some limited cover from the infected.
But, you know, if you wanna wait till sun-up
then you're as good as dead.
Who are you?
Sergeant Doyle. Delta rooftop unit.
Why aren't you at your post?
Why aren't you?
Look, you guys do what you want,
but I'm gonna get the fuck outta here.
You coming?
All right, come on.
- Less shooting.
- Maybe it's under control.
Or there are less shooters.
All right, listen. I need you guys
to look at me and only me, OK?
You run when I run.
Be my shadow. That's it, all right?
Get around back. Watch her.
Ready? Let's go.
Stay.
Doyle, come in.
- Flynn, go.
- Doyle, where the fuck are you, man?
- Ground level, District One.
- Shit. Close frequency.
Copy that.
What the fuck are you doing there?
You got some serious shit coming your way.
- We already got some serious shit.
- I'm not playing. This is worse.
The air cav just got their orders.
They're firebombing all of District One.
- That was fast.
- Outbreak is out of control.
They're taking no chances. So unless you are
out of the target zone, you are getting cooked.
- How long we got?
- They're on their way. Four minutes, tops.
But listen. I got some clear landing ground
at Regent's Park. That's the pick-up point.
- I'll be back in touch.
- Doyle, you fucking better be.
All right, look, guys, we gotta run.
Just stay low and stay fast, OK?
After me. Let's go.
- Snipers! Get down! Snipers!
- Back! Back! Back!
Get back! Get back!
Andy, get back!
- Back!
- Andy, get in!
- Shit.
- Fuck!
It's OK. It's just a flesh wound.
Multiple shots, one hit.
He's a panicker, no marksman.
OK.
- What's your name?
- Sam.
OK, Sam. Come here. Get closer.
Do you see that doorway?
I need you to run as fast as you can in a
zigzag like this, OK? Don't stop for anything.
- You want me to be bait?
- He'll take shots at you, but he'll miss.
He's gonna expose his position.
Means I get a shot at him. I won't miss.
- You're out of your fucking mind.
- Stay back.
Two minutes, we're all gonna die.
You want that?
No!
Andy!
Fuck!
Good work, kid.
- The fence!
- Watch it, watch it. Behind me.
Go! Go! Go!
Come on. Come on, come on.
Jump!
This is Red Fox One pouring whisky.
Keep going!
We'll be safe under the river.
Go! Go!
Come on. Come on!
Run! Run!
Bring in biological units.
Fan out from predesignated positions.
Bio units, copy.
Use of chemical weapons authorised.
Repeat, chemical weapons are authorised.
Stay close.
They left us again.
Do you think Mum's still alive?
Not this time.
- You look a little pale.
- Blood makes me nauseous.
You never answered my question.
About why you left your post.
When I got that boy in my sights.
That's not a target any more.
When we were separated...
I thought I'd lost you, too.
We won't get separated again.
We'll stay together, whatever happens.
Whatever happens.
It was all fucked.
You could hear it all over the radios. Fucked.
Anyway, what about you?
- Why the hell are you here?
- Their mother had very special blood.
A natural kind of immunity to the virus.
Not all genetic traits are passed on, you know.
They can skip a generation
or vanish altogether, but...
But they might have it.
It's a possibility.
So their lives are far more valuable than mine.
Or yours.
I got it.
Doyle!
- Flynn, go.
- You made it!
I knew you'd do it. Listen. I'm coming
to you right now, but keep a lookout.
There's sightings of infected
that have escaped the firebombing.
- Give me an ETA.
- About 60.
- Minutes?
- No. Seconds.
Kids, come on.
Get down. Down! Down!
I see you. I'm coming in.
Jesus, Doyle, you got people with you.
Who the fuck are those people?
Doyle! Who the fuck are those people?
I can't take 'em. We will be shot out of the sky
if I try to land at the base.
No, no, don't take 'em to base!
Take 'em over the Channel!
- What?
- We gotta get these kids outta here.
Get the fuck in, Doyle!
I'm not taking 'em!
- Get me out of here!
- Sam, come back!
Hey, get the fuck off there!
Get that fucker off my ski!
- OK, you wanna fly with me, asshole?
- Sam!
Come on!
Fuck!
We're gonna die down here!
Do something!
You wanna fuck?
Come on, you fuckers!
Get up! Run! Move it!
Don't look back! Keep going!
Keep going.
Fuck you, pussy!
Doyle, come in! Doyle!
You need to get to safe ground.
Get to the stadium. Ditch those people.
I'm not taking 'em.
Flynn, come in.
Flynn, I know you can hear me.
Fuck the Code Red, fuck the chain
of command. I need an extraction.
You better fucking be there, cos we will be.
You OK? Yeah?
I bet you're tired, huh? Me, too.
OK, I need you to help me, OK?
Help me with your sister. You got that?
Come on. Gotta go. Gotta go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Gas! Get back! Get back!
- Tammy, Andy, get in the car!
- It's gas! Run! Come on!
Come on, get in the car! Get in the car!
Come on! Get in! Get in!
Get in, Andy!
Go, go, go!
Lock the doors!
Get the vents, get the vents.
- It won't start!
- We'll be fine, all right? Just keep trying.
It won't start!
Come on, come on, come on.
Keep trying. Keep trying!
- It won't start! It won't fucking start!
- Fuck me!
- It won't start!
- Put your foot on the clutch.
All right. You pop the clutch when I tell you,
OK? You get them to the stadium. OK?
Keep your head down.
I'll meet you there.
OK.
- Doyle!
Pop it! Pop it!
Go! Go!
Go!
Oh, my God...
OK.
Fuck!
- Scarlet!
- Fuck!
They're shooting at us!
Hold on!
Shit.
OK, let's go.
Come on, through here, guys.
Just hold onto the rails.
Careful, guys.
OK.
It's OK. I can see. I can see.
Keep going down.
OK.
Just keep walking straight, guys.
Holding against the wall.
You're doing really well. You're doing great.
OK, get back! Get back against the wall!
OK. Good.
Just stay close. Slightly to the right, Andy.
It's OK. I can see. It's OK.
I've got the night sight on.
You're doing great. Just hold... hold the rail.
Nice and slow down the stairs, OK?
Stop! Stop! Stop right now!
OK, Tammy, to your left. Good.
OK. Good girl. Just straight down.
Nice and slow. Slower.
Stop! Stop, honey.
It's OK. It's OK. It's OK. All right?
Grab hold of the other railing, OK?
Go to your right.
- Scarlet, I can't see anything!
- Go to your right. Go to your right.
All right. Keep trying to skip... Just put your
leg far out in front of you, OK? Good girl.
Hold onto the rail. Careful!
Tammy!
Andy!
Where are you?
Andy! Where are you? Andy!
Answer me!
Where are you?
Tammy!
- Where are you?
- Scarlet!
- Tammy, I'm coming. I'm right here.
- Scarlet, I've lost Andy!
- I'm right here.
- I've lost Andy.
There we go.
Just come slowly towards me.
I've lost Andy.
We'll find Andy.
Scarlet!
Andy!
Where are you?
Scarlet.
Tammy?
Scarlet?
No!
Don!
We stay together - whatever happens.
- No!
- Andy!
Andy, no!
No! Andy!
Andy! Andy!
No!
Andy!
Tam, am I one of them?
No.
No, you're not.
Stop!
Where's Doyle?
It's just us.
Come on.
Get in. Come on.
Vous m'entendez?
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me? Hello? Can you hear me?
Is anybody there?
We need your help.
Répondez. Répondez.